Guide to the Cornell Adult University records, 1971-2009.
Cornell Adult University records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell Adult University records, 1971-2009.
41-8-3726
Cornell Adult University.
1.1 cubic ft.
Printed Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records of adult university offered by Cornell University, including course lists, compilations, announcements, and other related material.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
This continuing education program for Cornell alumni began July, 1968.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records of adult university offered by Cornell University, including course lists, compilations, announcements, and other related material.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell Adult University.; Cornell University--Alumni and alumnae.; Cornell University--Students.; Cornell University--Faculty.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Study Tour Brochures, 1973, 1972, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Study Tour Brochures, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Study Tour Brochures, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Study Tour Brochures, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Study Tour Brochures, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Study Tour Brochures, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Study Tour Brochures, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Study Tour Brochures, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Study Tour Brochures, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Study Tour Brochures, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Study Tour Brochures, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Youth Program Brochures, Summers 1997, 2000-2004 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Early-Bird Program Announcement, 1990-1996 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Early-Bird Program Announcement, 1998-2003, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Early-Bird Program Announcement, 1985-1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Study Tour Brochures- Weekend Seminars, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Study Tour Brochures, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Study Tour Brochures, 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Study Tour Brochures, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Compilation for the Geology of the Lesser Antilles Tour, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Compilation of the Galapagos Islands, January 1987 (Box 2)
- Youth Tour Brochures, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Program Catalogs, 1982, 1981, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Program Catalogs, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Program for Summer and September, 1987 (Box 2)
- Program Catalogs, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Program Catalogs, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Program Catalogs, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Program Catalogs, Fall 1991- Spring 1992 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Compilation for the Geology of New Zealand Tour, January 1992 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Program Catalogs, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Program Catalogs, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Compilation for the Geology of the Mediterranean Tour, July 1994 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Program Catalogs, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Program Catalogs, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Program Catalogs, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Program Catalogs, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Program Catalogs, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Program Catalogs, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Program Catalogs, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Program Catalogs, 2002-2004 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Program Catalogs, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Program Catalogs, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Program Catalogs, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Program Catalogs, 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Program Catalogs, 2007, 2009, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Handout for Marine Fishes of Hawaii and Central Pacific Ocean Tour (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Negatives and Contact Sheets of Events-photos by Robert MacDougall, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 46)